Samuel Dash Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Writings File, 1748-2004 (Box 239-252)
  - Books
    - The Intruders: Unreasonable Searches and Seizures from King John to John Ashcroft (Box 241)
      - Research material
        - Cases
          - Massachusetts cases, 1852-1860, 1886, 1903-1906
          - Miscellaneous, 1971-1978, 1984-1991, undated
          - Nardone v. United States, 1936-1950, 1986, undated
          - Olmstead v. United States, 1924-1928, 1937, 1943, 1966, undated, (1 folder) (Box 244)
          - Rathbun v. United States, 1956-1957, 1992, undated
          - Stop and frisk, 1994-1995, undated, (2 folders)
          - United States v. Banks, 2003, (2 folders)
          - Weeks v. United States (Box 245)
            - Group 1, 1829, 1836, 1877, 1897, 1903-1905, 1911-1912
            - Group 2, 1911-1914, 1925, 1944, 1949, 1962
            - Group 3, 1913-1914, undated
          - Wolf v. Colorado, 1939-1964, undated
          - Wong Sun v. United States, 1959-1963, 1988, undated, (2 folders)
        - Esser, Kurt, “The Admissibility of Illegally Obtained Search and Seizure Evidence–An Australian-American Comparative Study,” undated
      - Fourth Amendment, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 246)
        - Miscellaneous, 1965, 1972, 1983, 1994-2001, undated
        - Notebook, Audrey L. Harris, 2000
        - Reviews, 2003-2004
    - Justice Denied: A Challenge to Lord Widgery's Report on “Bloody Sunday”
      - Articles and clippings, 1972, 1998, undated, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973, undated, (5 folders) (Box 247)
      - List of those receiving the report, 1971, undated
      - Maps, 1967-1972
      - National Council for Civil Liberties files, 1972
        - Set 3
          - Death
            - Duddy
            - Gilmore
            - McGuigan
            - Donaghy and McKinney
            - Kelly, Nash, Young, and McDaid (Box 248)
          - Wounding
            - Bridges
            - Burke
            - Deery
            - Donaghy and Johnson
            - Friel and Nash (senior)
            - Miscellaneous
        - Set 6
          - Arrests
          - Death
            - Doherty
            - Donaghy and McKinney
            - Gilmore
            - Kelly, Nash, Young, and McDaid
            - McElhinney
            - McGuigan
            - Wray
          - General
            - Chamberlain Street (C-O)
            - Free Derry Corner (F-O)
            - Glenfada Park (G-O) (Box 249)
            - Miscellany (M-O)
            - Rossville Flats/Joseph Place (J-O)
            - Rossville Flats/Waste Ground (W-O)
            - Rossville Street (R-O)
            - Sackville Street/William Street (S-O)
          - Introduction
          - Notes
          - Wounding
            - Bridges
            - Burke
            - Deery
            - Donaghy and Johnson
            - Friel and Nash (senior)
            - Miscellaneous
      - Printed matter, 1971-1974, (4 folders)
      - Reports
        - Dash, Samuel
          - Drafts and notes, 1972, (2 folders)
          - Final, 1972, undated, (2 folders) (Box 250)
        - Widgery, John Passmore, Baron, 1972
      - Study on firearms discharge residues, 1959, 1965-1972
      - Transcripts, 1972, Feb.-Mar.
        - Days 1-6, (3 folders)
        - Days 7-14, (6 folders) (Box 251)
        - Days 15-20, (4 folders) (Box 252)
  - Miscellany, 1987-1989, undated
  - Play, Alexander the Great, 2003
  - Poems, 1946, 1987-2003, undated
- Grand Jury File (Closed), circa 1995-circa 1998 (Box X 253)
  Sealed grand jury material related to the Whitewater Inquiry.
  - circa 1995-circa 1998 (Box X 253)
- Top Secret, 1970 (Box TS 1)
  Memorandum.
  Arranged and described according to the series, container, and folder from which the item was removed.
  - Government Investigations (Box TS 1)
    - Watergate Affair
      - Exhibits
        - Memoranda, Haldeman to Huston, 1970
        - Memoranda, Huston to Haldeman, 1970 See SCI
        - Monograph, Operational Restraints on Intelligence Collection, circa 1970 See SCI
- Sensitive Compartmented Information, 1970 (Box SCI 1)
  Memorandum and a monograph.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Government Investigations (Box SCI 1)
    - Watergate Affair
      - Exhibits
        - Memoranda, Huston to Haldeman, 1970
        - Monograph, Operational Restraints on Intelligence Collection, circa 1970